completely disappointing family
familia completamente decepcionante
completely disappointing
completamente decepcionante
once again okay they have
una vez más vale me han vuelto a
disappointed me again the boy completely
decepcionar el chico completamente
hurt and completely disappointed I did not
dolido y completamente decepcionado no
expect anything absolutely at all
me esperaba nada absolutamente para nada
this reaction from this person
esta reacción por parte de esta persona
who acts like a calm, peaceful person
que se las da de persona tranquila
and so on okay Albert Domenech
sosegada y demás vale Albert domenech ha
responded to last night's video with
respondido al vídeo de anoche con
insults okay he has fallen into insults he has
insultos vale ha caído en el insulto ha
fallen into insults not only with me
caído en el insulto no solamente conmigo
but disrespecting with bad
sino faltando al respeto con malas
answers also to my followers
contestaciones también a mis seguidores
I would have liked to see what the
a mí me hubiera gustado ver a las
fans
fanáticas
would be saying if I had
que estarían diciendo si yo hubiera
said 50% of the things that
dicho el 50% de las cosas que ha dicho
Albert said today okay I
Albert hoy vale
invite you all to watch the
os invito a todos a que veáis el
excerpt from yesterday okay I simply did not
extracto de ayer vale yo simplemente no
agree with his video there are other
estaba de acuerdo con su vídeo hay otras
occasions in which I have applauded him
ocasiones en las que le he aplaudido
both on Twitter and on YouTube I have
tanto en Twitter como en YouTube le he
promoted a lot of things and there he
promocionado un montón de cosas y ahí
has never complained that I talk about his
nunca se ha quejado de que hable de sus
videos at the moment that I have not
vídeos en el momento que no he estado de
agreed because I know that not even he himself
acuerdo porque sé que ni él mismo está
agrees with what he said yesterday he
de acuerdo con lo que dijo ayer
has fallen into insults okay here you
ha caído en el insulto vale aquí lo
have it Look Well I
tenéis Mirad
tell you by the face you are very
Pues a la carita te lo digo eres muy
dirty  you set
sucio
this on fire You have provoked
tú has incendiado esto tú Has provocado
the actors to take them to your
a los actores para llevarlos a tu
field And you will drown in the mud in
terreno Y tú te ahogarás en el fango al
time I wish you good luck because you are
tiempo te deseo mucha suerte porque la
going to need it I
vas a necesitar
invite you to see the extract from
yo os invito a que veáis el extracto de
yesterday okay take apart all the things he
ayer vale desmonte todas las cosas que
said without any disrespect okay I
dijo sin ninguna falta de respeto vale
don't understand why when he has seen himself
No entiendo por qué cuando se ha visto
cornered and when he has seen himself upset
acorralado y cuando se ha vistofuscado
with this sack I mean he is answering me he
con este saca O sea me está contestando
even
hasta
has to insult me ​​okay or so
me tiene que insultar vale o sea
basically what I have done today
básicamente lo que yo he hecho hoy
after he was since
después de que él estuviera desde por la
morning throwing chicks
mañana tirando pollitas
because I don't like the chicks
porque a mí la pullita no me gustan a mí
I like to clarify things up
me gusta aclarar las cosas
front not talking dialoguing I have
de frente no hablando dialogando le he
challenged him to a debate more than challenging him I have
retado a un debate más que retarle le he
invited him to come to my channel to have
invitado a que venga a mi canal a tener
a chat there are many people who are
una charla hay mucha gente que está
criticizing that I challenge him to a debate
criticando que yo le reto a un debate
saying that I am believing I am
diciendo que estoy creyendo estoy
wanting to create a spectacle
queriendo crear espectáculo
when they applauded and called him a coward
cuando aplaudieron y llamaron cobarde
here with Hernandez When Antonio David
aquí con Hernández Cuando Antonio David
challenged him in a debate on his channel okay it is not
le reton debate en su canal vale no se
about what he does it is about
trata de qué es lo que haga se trata de
who does it okay I think the most
quién lo haga vale Yo creo que lo más
logical thing if  there is a lack of understanding
lógico si hay una falta de entendimiento
Maybe or a misunderstanding or
A lo mejor o un mal entendido o
difference of opinions I believe that the
diferencia de opiniones yo creo que lo
noblest and most honest thing is to debate it
más noble y lo más honesto es debatirlo
exchange opinions from respect
intercambiar opiniones desde el respeto
in a forum where we have the right to
en un foro donde tengamos derecho a
reply there is no manipulation because
réplica no haya manipulaciones porque
we are in public and we discuss what we
estamos en público y discutamos lo que
have to discuss as long as we do not
tengamos que discutir mientras que no
disrespect each other Okay and Albert
nos faltemos el respeto Vale y Albert me
has answered me with my life is not a face to
ha contestado con mi vida no es un cara
face on a YouTube channel and you know it
a cara en un canal de YouTube y lo sabes
when he put this to me that my life
cuando me ha puesto esto de que mi vida
is not a face to face on a
no es un cara a cara en un canal de
YouTube channel Well I have answered him with
YouTube Pues yo le he contestado con
this clip
este clip
some person decides
alguna persona decide
of those alluded to or those alluded to that they
de los aludidos o aludidas que quiere
feel the need to say something
que siente la necesidad de decir algo
This is the way
Esta es la vía
the way of the uncovered face there was not the one
la vía de la cara destapada no la había
of the
de los
organizational charts or this [ __ ] what is it
organigramas o la [__] esta como se
called what is put on Twitter that
llama lo que se pone en Twitter que la
people do not show their faces and then it is very
gente no no da la cara y entonces es muy
easy to accuse and insult people
fácil acusar e insultar a la gente
when you do not have no no no the face the little face the little face
cuando tú no tienes no no no la cara la
and if I do not
carita la carita la carita y si no os
tell you my address in the vanguard and you
digo mi dirección en la vanguardia y me
come see me physically or if not  you are
venís a ver físicamente o si no me dáis
alone and I will come to see you in Madrid or
sola y os vengo a ver yo a Madrid a
Malaga wherever necessary but face to face
Málaga donde haga falta pero la carita
some person to face to face I would
alguna persona a la carita a la carita
love to see I would love to see the
Me encantaría ver Me encantaría ver la
reaction of all the people who are
reacción de toda la gente que se me está
throwing themselves at me these days if it
echando encima en estos días si a mí se
crossed my mind to
me pasara por la cabeza
challenge the people who are
retar a la gente que me está llevando la
contradicting me on Twitter and in all these
contraria en Twitter y en todos estos
places challenge them to see us in person to talk about
lugares retarles a vernos en personas a
it face to face I
que lo hablemos en la carita Me
would love well I would love to see how they would be
encantaría bien me encantaría ver cómo
eating me I would love but
me estarían comiendo Me encantaría pero
as I just told you it is not about
como os acabo de decir no se trata del
what but about who okay simply what I have
qué sino el quién vale simplemente lo
done has been done the most
que he hecho ha sido hecho el más
responded that he does not want to have a debate
respondió que no quiere hacer un debate
because his life is not face to face I
porque su vida no es un cara a cara le
answered him with this clip because he is a
contestaba con este clip porque es un
face to face when it suits him And since he
cara cara cuando le interesa Y como se
has seen himself frustrated and cornered he has
ha visto fuscado y acorralado me ha
insulted me he has fallen into the insult okay I
insultado ha caído en el insulto vale os
am going to tell you the whole story from
voy a contar la historia completa desde
the beginning I am going to give you the
el principio os voy a poner la historia
whole story from the beginning so that you
completa desde el principio para que
can see how the thing started okay He has been putting barbs
veáis cómo ha empezado la movida vale Él
since this morning do a
lleva desde por la mañana poniendo puyas
live of  3 hours and then a
márcate un directo de 3 horas y luego un
space Well, nothing Sorry My irony if it
espacio Pues nada Disculpa Mi ironía si
bothered you tell me What you don't
te ha molestado ya me dirás En qué no
agree with in a video in which I
estás de acuerdo en un vídeo en el que
say that I don't want to take a position it's a lie if you take a
digo que no quiero posicionarme mentira
position in the video what you do
te posiciones en el vídeo lo que haces
is make your position clear and that they have
es dejar Clara tu postura y que tienen
the same word for word the same
la misma palabra por palabra la misma
opinion of the fanatic so that they don't
opinión de la fanática para que no te
accuse you of the opposite and
tachen de lo contrario
then receive three hours of
para luego recibir tres horas de
prejudice from the others
prejuicio por parte de los demás
new video this one cost me more
nuevo vídeo este me ha costado más
because the notes
porque no habían llegado aún los apuntes
from Antonio's fans hadn't arrived yet there was time
de las fanáticas de Antonio había tiempo
and I didn't know what to say I'm
y no sabía qué decir
going to tell you because you deserve it
os lo voy a contar por con lo merecéis
the Malaga gummy bears had
las gominolas de Málaga tenían
burundanga and I fell asleep a monkey
burundanga y me quedé dormido un mono
in a blue t-shirt undressed me and
con la camiseta azul me desvistió y
they put a double in my place the guy has
pusieron un doble en mi lugar el tío
now become a youtuber thanks to the
ahora se ha hecho youtuber gracias a los
two founders of the j&amp;j platform an
dos fundadores de la plataforma j&amp;j un
axe a person who doesn't enter is worth a
hacha una persona que no entra vale una
person who doesn't want to enter doesn't spend
persona que no quiere entrar no se pega
all day putting barbs to put
todo el día poniendo puyas para poner
barbs I prefer to debate face to face I
puyas yo prefiero debatir cara a cara
insist on a live forum where it can't be
insisto en un foro en directo donde no
manipulated and  where we all
se pueda manipular y donde todos
have the right to reply and everything is
tengamos derecho a réplica y quede todo
exposed so that it can't be manipulated
expuesto para que no se pueda manipular
because this is an example but in
porque esto es un ejemplo pero en otros
many other tweets that you've posted today during
muchos tweet que has puesto hoy durante
the day he said that I manipulated yesterday
el día ha dicho que yo ayer manipulé
when literally what I did was
cuando literalmente lo que hice fue
react to his video and compare them with a
reaccionar a su vídeo y compararlos con
clip showing that he has criticized
clip demostrando que él sí ha criticado
colleagues Apart from the fact that it's [ __ ] okay you
a compañeros Aparte que es una chorrada
can criticize colleagues
vale se puede criticar a compañeros
because he does it, I mean he sticks around all
porque él lo hace o sea se pega todo el
day and his channel is about criticizing
día y su canal trata sobre criticar a
other journalists and
otros periodistas y
complicating people on YouTube he
complicado a gente de YouTube ha
criticized Diego arrabal has criticized Wow he
criticado Diego arrabal ha criticado Wow
has criticized a lot of YouTube it was
ha criticado un montón de YouTube era
Maika he criticized the guy with the cap he
Maika ha criticado al de la gorra ha
criticized the pizza guy he has given nicknames he has
criticado al pizzero ha puesto motes se
messed with the physicist I mean what balls
ha metido con el físico O sea qué huevos
what balls and with all the love because I don't dislike him
qué huevos y con todo el cariño porque
but what balls what balls
no me cae mal pero qué huevos qué huevos
and dirty laundry is washed at home
y que los trapos sucios se lavan en casa
if the dirty laundry that you don't want to be
si los trapos sucios que tú no quieres
washed is Antonio David's
que se laven son los de Antonio David
because you're with the tide and you have those
porque estás con la marea y tienes esos
followers But you expose the
seguidores Pero tú expones los trapos
dirty laundry that you want and I
sucios que a ti te dan la gana y lo
proved it yesterday with a click okay If you don't
demostré ayer con clic vale Si no me
know me  when he's having an argument and you don't
sabes cuando te está con argumento y no
want to accept a debate I understand
quieres aceptar un debate lo entiendo
but don't insult me ​​and especially don't
pero no me insulte y sobre todo no
insult my followers okay because
insultes a mis seguidores vale porque
look at the things he's been dedicated to
mirar las cosas que se ha dedicado a
saying eh No Money is not the argument
decir eh No El dinero no es el argumento
and you know it the argument is because I don't feel like
y lo sabes el argumento es porque no me
Kinders eggs Oh oh yeah
sale de los huevos kinders Ay Ay si
take out the privates come on man
sacar a los privados venga hombre Aquí
Not here, here he doesn't wash his dirty laundry at home
no aquí no lava los trapo sucios en casa
okay here he washes it wherever he wants to
vale aquí los lava donde él quiera a
anonymous people or in other words he's
gente anónima o sea esto se lo está
telling this followers to followers Oh yeah I
diciendo seguidoras a seguidoras Ay si
take out the privates you know that when he's
saco los privados sabéis que cuando me
insulted me you know what
ha insultado sabéis qué es lo que han
people have done
la gente
exactly what you deserve Oliveira Look
justo lo que te mereces oliveira Mira
Javi Oliveira has nothing to do
Javi oliveira no tiene nada que hacer
with Albert first Respect his
con Albert primero Respeta a sus
followers then analyze what's happening
seguidores luego analiza lo que ocurre
don't get angry about Malaga because he did
no se enfada por lo de Málaga porque él
n't meet with you and he doesn't find
ni se reunió con vosotros
out a [ __ ] thing dude
ni se entera una [__] [__] tío
he's literally in the photo and in the
literalmente él está en la foto y en el
video he was with us
vídeo estuvo con nosotros
he ate but with his people he doesn't act like a
él comió pero con su gente no hace como
cap he calls us crazy and you Why
gorra que nos llama locas y tú Para qué
remember Albert don't lower your level because it's
recordar Albert no bajes tu nivel porque
not worth it you're the greatest he's
no merece la pena eres el más grande es
dirty and mean Albert don't enter
sucio y ruin Albert no entres al trapo
Bravo rag Albert you are very big
Bravo Albert eres muy grande
I can do whatever the hell I want
yo puedo hacer lo que me salga del Moño
criticize Oliveira and tell him to [ __ ] off
criticar oliveira y mandar a la [__]
Oh and I don't cry for Javi I laugh at his
Ah y por Javi no lloro me río de su
intelligence
inteligencia
applause Albert you are in the first division
aplausos Albert tú eres primera división
they are from the neighborhood he
ellos son de barrio
says dirty is an insult you are only describing him that is what you want Javi debate Javi he really likes the circus This is the blue tide but nevertheless he does not care that Antonio David also challenges him to debate Well the fact is that Antonio David has been debating with people on
David lleva debatiendo con gente en
television his whole life How great
televisión toda la vida Qué grande
honest illegal you are
honesto ilegal eres
very well said applause
muy bien dicho aplausos
Albert Domenech a 10
Albert domenech un 10
Bravo
Bravo
olé you Javi the dirty one does not deserve any
olé tú Javi el sucio no se merece ningún
respect you are short in the
respeto eres cortita en el Twitter
previous Twitter I tell you very clearly I mean
anterior te lo digo bien clarito o sea
imagine applause and more applause for the
imaginaros aplausos y más aplausos al
insult you have a lot of class imagine
insulto tú tienes mucha clase imaginaros
that these are the people who complain about
que esta es la gente que se queja de que
Rocío Flores being insulted on social networks that I
insulten en redes a Rocío flores que yo
am the first to condemn and I
soy el primero que lo condena Y lo
will continue to condemn it of course but
seguiré condenando por supuesto pero
imagine that the people who are
imaginaros que la gente que está
condemning the insults
condenando los insultos
applaud them  insults if they go to others they
aplaude los insultos si van a otros
applaud the insults to people who are
aplauden los insultos a gente que es
critical of Antonio David and I'm not even
crítica con Antonio David y ni siquiera
critical of Antonio vivamos the only thing I've
soy crítico con Antonio vivamos lo único
said is that he disappointed me I
que he dicho es que me ha decepcionado O
mean it's not like I'm against him
sea no es como que esté en contra de él
or that I'm going to become a fuchsia tide or
ni que me vaya a volver marea fucsia ni
anything like that I'm simply
nada por el estilo Simplemente soy
objective and neutral I
objetivo y neutral
mean these people applaud those insults
o sea esta gente aplauden esos insultos
here you have the beginning of the discussion
aquí tenéis el comienzo de la discusión
on Twitter well I'm starting after
en Twitter bueno comienzo después de que
he spent all [ __ ] day throwing
él llevara todo el [__] día lanzando
barbs really from my point of view it
pullas de verdad bajo mi punto de vista
's always better to talk face to face and
siempre es mejor hablar a la cara y en
live to avoid confusion
directo para no dar lugar a confusión en
instead of going with innuendos I mean throwing
lugar de ir con indirectas o sea tirar
the stone and hiding your hand it wasn't
la piedra y esconder la mano no ha sido
an attack it was a response to your
un ataque ha sido una respuesta a tu
video if you don't agree and you
vídeo si no estás de acuerdo y lo
want to refute it I'll be live until the afternoon
quieres rebatir estaré hasta la tarde en
okay And he answered me with the
directo vale Y él me ha contestado con
thing about my life not being a face to face on a
lo de mi vida no es un cara a cara en un
YouTube channel which is good that I've already
canal de YouTube cosa que bueno que ya
put a click on it the clip is tremendous
os he puesto un clic que es tremendo el
not the excuses for not debating the
clip no las excusas para no debatir la
excuse for not debating instead of saying I
excusa para no debatir en vez de decir
have nothing to answer because  I'm not
no tengo nada que responder porque no
going to be able to answer
voy a poder responder
clearly and on his channel and make money
claro y en su canal y que haga dinerito
there
allí
to see stones nonsense when we could have
a ver piedras chorrada cuando podíamos
done it both channels and then
haberlo hecho los dos canales y luego
upload them both channels or whatever
subirlos los dos canales o lo que
you want You know that for the money it is not to
quieras Sabes que por el dinero no es
clarify and to have an exchange
por aclarar y por hacer un intercambio
of opinions Hey the debates are healthy
de opiniones Oye los debates son sanos
what happens is that of course they are only so that I
lo que pasa es que claro son solamente
can answer
que pueda responder
this comment I don't know if you are going to
este comentario No sé si ustedes lo Vais
understand it the same as me but the
a entender igual que yo pero el
comment Yes I understand it if I am not
comentario Si lo entiendo si no lo estoy
misunderstanding
entendiendo mal
if I am not misunderstanding it I find it
si no lo estoy entendiendo mal me parece
repulsive okay you
repulsivo vale
lack memory friends I have been flying free for a long time
os falta memoria amigas hace tiempo que
and I have criticized all
vuelo libre y que critico todas las
sides a long time when others
partes mucho tiempo cuando otros
adored hoses
adoraban mangueras
that how do you understand about they
que cómo entendéis usted de lo de
adored hoses because I understand it
adoraban mangueras porque yo lo entiendo
quite inappropriate they adored hoses
bastante inapropiado adoraban mangueras
people are applauding Okay when has he
la gente está aplaudiendo Vale cuando le
put some follower Oh if I take out
ha puesto alguna seguidora Ay si saco
the privates I have answered him Albert
los privados le he contestado yo Albert
the dirty laundry is cleaned at home and
los trapos sucios se limpian en casa y
with all his balls because you have to have
con todo su huevazo porque hay que tener
balls after the clicks we saw
huevazo después de los clics que vimos
yesterday and many more that I have reserved for myself the
ayer y muchos más que me he reservado el
guy with  her egg lays Exactly That's how I
tío con su huevo pone Exacto Así me
like you to learn from me
gusta que aprendas de mí
to learn from me when I see you don't wash your
que aprendas de mí al ver tú no lavas
dirty laundry at home
los trapos sucios en casa
you tell your private things when it
tú cuentas las cosas privadas cuando a
interests you Look Marta risk
ti te interesa Mira Marta riesgo te
called you on the phone
llamó por teléfono
messing around messing around because you give several
liándotela liándotela porque das varios
details throughout the video Here I'm going to
detalles a lo largo del vídeo Aquí voy a
put a clip to give an example
poner un clip por poner ejemplo
and in what she is a journalist to doesn't know doesn't know
y en qué es periodista a no sabe no sepa
what bothers a
lo que molesta precisamente a un
journalist precisely when they call you to tell you
periodista que le llamen para decirle
how to do your job
cómo tiene que hacer su trabajo
why you can make a video When
por qué tú puedes hacer un vídeo Cuando
someone calls you messing around because you
alguien te llama liándotela porque tú sí
can make a video When someone
puedes hacer un vídeo Cuando alguien te
calls you messing around
llama liándotela
country of my opinion
país de mi opinión
I have always offered you the space in
Yo siempre os he ofrecido el espacio en
its day I offered it to her for example Alexia and
su día se lo ofrecí por ejemplo Alexia y
in a very rude way she never ever ever
de una forma muy mal educada jamás jamás
gave me a reason as to why she had
me dio un motivo del Por qué me había
left me stranded week after week
dejado tirado semana tras semana
here as she is lost khaleesi up
aquí como está perdido khaleesi arriba
no le you have not done an interview
no le no le has hecho una entrevista
maybe she started telling things that
igual se puso a contar cosas que le
had happened to her in private with Alexia she did not
había pasado en privado con Alexia no
wash the dirty laundry at home and now
lavó los trapos sucios en casa y ahora
the same with
lo mismo con
WhatsApp I am little calls I do not insist not
WhatsApp soy llamaditas no insisto no
for the words  the tones the little tones
por las palabras los tonos los tonitos
why can you say that Marta
por qué tú puedes contar que Marta
risk has called you messing things up and Juanjo
riesgo te ha llamado liándotela y Juanjo
can't tell Antonio David is his
no puede contarse Antonio David se le
ally it is completely false that
Aliado a él es completamente falso que
you are one to wash dirty laundry at
tú seas de lavar los trapos sucios en
home That opinion is made because they are the ones that
casa Esa opinión la hace porque son las
the fanatics repeat because they don't
que repiten las fanáticas porque no
want something to come to light that leaves
quieren que salga la luz algo que deje
Antonio David in a bad light okay or rather you don't wash
mal Antonio David vale o sea no lavas
dirty laundry at home Only those
los trapos sucios en casa Solamente los
that you love those that are not interesting
que tú los quieres los que no interesan
yes there are common followers who have
sí que hay seguidores en común que se
felt disappointed with Albert not
han sentido decepcionados con Albert no
when he has insulted because he has gone crazy he has felt
cuando ha insultado porque se le ha ido
frustrated he has felt
la olla se ha frustrado se ha sentido
frustrated because they had given him a sack
frustrado porque le habían dado un saca
one after another Better said One after another
uno tras otro Mejor dicho Uno tras otro
and he has had to resort to insult okay
y ha tenido que recurrir al insulto vale
and they have told him that they are
y le han dicho que que están
disappointed and he takes and puts with all
decepcionados y coge y pone con todos
his balls he has said worse things to me I
sus huevazos me ha dicho cosas peores yo
invite you all and I have been doing it for
os invito a todos y lo llevo haciendo
weeks to all of you who are with the
semanas a todos los que estáis con el
mantra because you have no argument of it is that they have
mantra porque no tenéis argumento de es
insulted us I have been asking for weeks to
que nos han insultado llevo semanas
tell me where and I
pidiendo que me indiquéis dónde y os
will apologize and Albert of all the
pediré disculpas y Albert de todo el
live yesterday I challenge you that you're not going to
directo ayer te reto que no vas a
answer but I challenge you to send me
contestar pero Te reto a que me envíes
where I've said worse things to you where I've
donde te he dicho cosas peores dónde te
said worse things to you than what you
he dicho cosas peores que las que me has
said to me today on Twitter that I love
dicho tú hoy en Twitter que adoro
hoses that I'm dirty
mangueras que soy un sucio
and making fun of the j&amp;j this is a
y cachondeándote de los j&amp;j esto es un
false mantra that they created because they
falso mantra que han creado porque no
have no arguments Okay
tienen argumentos Vale
when I posted a tweet asking
cuando he puesto un tweet preguntándole
the tide it
a la marea
would be considered disrespectful insults
consideraría y falta de respeto insultos
if I came up with my live streams Calling my
si se me ocurrieran mis directos Llamar
kindergarten classmates answering
a los compañeros parvularios contestarle
the audience with it doesn't come out of my
a la audiencia con no me sale de los
balls and social maturity or that your
huevos y madurez social o que vuestras
opinions are a joke which are some
opiniones son de chiste que son algunas
of the things they posted today on
de las cosas que han puesto hoy en
Twitter and they turn me on Sorry you say
Twitter y me ponen Perdona tú dices
worse things and I said let's see
cosas peores y le he dicho a ver qué
what I say worse I'm interested in your opinion
cosa digo yo peor me interesa tu opinión
and it disappeared I mean when you
y ha desapareció o sea cuando tú le
ask them they're like those from Telecinco with
preguntas son como los de telecinco con
the looks operation Okay when when
la operación de looks Vale cuando cuando
you want Telecinco not to broadcast not to record you
tú quieras que telecinco no emita no te
on the street or something you
grabe por la calle o algo eso tú le
tell them light operation light operation
dices operación de luz operación de luz
and they delete the videos Okay so these people
y borran los vídeos Vale pues esta gente
every time they come I tell them let's see
cada vez que viene le digo a ver
Show me the clips where I have insulted you
Enséñame los clips donde te he insultado
and they disappear because it is a mantra that is a
y desaparecen porque es un mantra que es
lie of course this has been a
mentira por supuesto esto ha sido una
disappointment and a disappointment
desilusión y una decepción más una
more a disappointment because the truth is that I have
decepción más porque de verdad que le ha
helped him in everything that I could not to
ayudado en todo lo que he podido no por
throw it in his face but I think that he could have
echarlo en cara pero creo que podía
argued with respect and not
haber argumentado con respeto y no
disrespect with insults to me and
faltando al respeto con insultos a mí y
my followers but once again
a mis seguidores pero una vez más pues
someone who I believed was
alguien que yo creía que era de otra
different shows his paw I have been
manera enseña la patita
on YouTube for many years and these
llevo muchos años en YouTube y estas
things have happened to me tons of times
cosas me han pasado montones de veces
okay these things come because the
vale estas cosas vienen porque los
numbers are very bad okay the numbers
números son muy malos vale los números
on YouTube translate the numbers on
en YouTube se traducen los números en
YouTube translate into followers
YouTube se traducen en seguidores
views and therefore money okay And
visitas y por lo tanto dinero vale Y el
losing losing them is
perder el perderlos
scary it is scary okay It's not worth it I have
pues da miedo da miedo vale Yo no vale
already been showing you these days
Yo ya os he estado enseñando estos días
that I do not bend or threaten or anything I
que no me doblego ni amenazas ni a nada
can stay I can stay alone that I will
me puedo quedar me puedo quedar solo que
continue to maintain my position and my
voy a seguir manteniendo mi postura y mi
opinion okay I can stay alone I have never
opinión vale me puedo quedar solo nunca
done it and I will not do it Now as if
lo he hecho y no lo haré Ahora como si
all those who came after
se van todos los que vinieron después
the docuseries are leaving okay to think How many
del docu serie vale pensar Cuántos
followers did I already have before the
seguidores tenía yo ya antes de la
docuseries and what if they all left, which
docuserie y que si se fueran todos que
won't be the case, but if they all left, I would still be
no será el caso pero si se fueran todos
happy on the internet. Okay, I mean, I'm not going to
seguiría tranquilamente en internet vale
give in if someone else
o sea no me voy a doblegar si otro se
gives in and they're weaker. Well, it's not
doblega y son más débiles Pues yo no
worth it. Even if I'm left alone and I know I'm the one who's getting the
vale Aunque me quede solo y sé que soy
most involved. I know I'm the one
el que más se está mojando Sé que soy el
who's getting the most involved, but that's why, out of
que más se está mojando pero es por eso
fear of followers, I don't know if in the end,
por miedo a seguidores no sé si al final
or from Malaga, they're going to tell it or not. I'm not going to tell it.
o de Málaga lo van a contar o no lo van
In fact, I
a contar yo no lo voy a contar De hecho
've been condemning it from the beginning that it be
estoy condenando desde un principio que
told, but I think since there's
se cuente pero yo creo que ya que hay
speculation it would be good if it were told.
especulaciones estaría bien que se conta
I'm not going hand in hand with another colleague
Yo no voy de la mano con otro compañero
with whom I've been killing myself. I've
con el que me he estado matando yo me he
said what I had to say with
dicho lo que me he tenido que decir con
that other colleague and right now we're
ese otro compañero y ahora mismo estamos
at peace because, you know, he's complaining
en paz porque sabéis está quejando de
that I'm fighting all the time. Okay,
que me esté peleando todo el tiempo vale
I want things to be cleared up, and
Yo quiero ya que se aclaren las cosas y
once things are cleared up and
una vez que se aclaren las cosas y salga
what really happened comes out, then I'll give my
lo que realmente pasó pues yo daré mi
point of view. In my opinion, maybe it's
punto de vista En mi opinión a lo mejor
not that one looks bad and the other looks bad
no es que quede mal uno y que quede mal
because it's telling me a lot.  how
otro porque me está diciendo mucho cómo
is it that before you said that one looked bad
es que antes decías que quedaba mal uno
and then the other Maybe
y luego el otro A lo mejor quedan más
both are more but what I think is that
los dos pero lo que yo creo que antes de
before all the speculation that there is and the
ante toda la especulación que hay y las
insinuations that many people are making
insinuaciones que está haciendo mucha
because they believe things okay I think it would
gente porque se creen cosas vale Yo creo
be best to clarify it but if they do
que lo mejor sería aclararlo pero que si
n't tell it I'm not going to
no lo cuentan yo no voy a ser que lo
tell it because it's something that I
cuente porque es algo que no de lo que
'm not the protagonist of, I'm
no soy el protagonista
not going to tell it okay If someone
no lo voy a contar yo vale Si alguien lo
tells it then I will give my explanations if they do
cuenta pues yo daré mis explicaciones si
n't tell it Well I'm not going to say
no lo cuentan Pues yo no voy a decir
anything okay from now on then I'm going to ignore
nada vale a partir de ahora pues paso de
everything like I always say or rather I'm going to ignore
todo como siempre digo o sea paso de
all these people I'm not going to shake
todas estas gentes ya no le doy la mano
anyone's hand anymore
a más nadie ya no le doy la mano más
because here on YouTube There
nadie porque aquí en YouTube Nada más
are nothing but interested groups, groups of
que hay pandas interesados pandas de
interested people who are not capable of getting their hands
interesados que no son capaces luego de
dirty and saying what they really
mojarse y de decir lo que realmente
think and feel for fear of
piensan y sienten por miedo a las
pressure right now this video is going to
presiones ahora mismo pues este vídeo va
have a lot of dislikes Because
a tener un montón de dislike Porque
right now they are in the easy position
ahora mismo están en la postura fácil
they are on the supported side okay but I don't care, I don't care,
están en el lado apoyado vale pero me da
I'm not
igual me da igual yo no soy ningún
interested and I'm not going to move for money
interesado ni me voy a mover por dinero
or followers or to have  more
ni por seguidores ni por tener más
visits not even for fear of being bullied
visitas ni por miedo a que machanten
okay never back down it's always the
vale jamás achantarse siempre es la
last option okay but yes I'll tell you
última opción vale pero sí que os digo
one thing
una cosa
once what's been said If it's
ya una vez expuesto lo expuesto Si
ever told
alguna vez se cuenta
Give my opinion and I'll clarify it and if it's not
Dale mi opinión y os la aclararé y si no
told each one their own way okay I'll
se cuentan por cada una su bola vale
continue with gossip TV for me the
sigo con tele salseo por mí se acaba el
topic ends Here the Malaga topic ends
tema Aquí se acaba el tema de Málaga
Here too if I don't know if anyone
Aquí también a no sé que alguien lo
tells it
cuente
the Malaga topic ends and the
se acaba el tema de Málaga y se acaba el
topic of these people ends okay gossip TV
tema de esta gente vale teles salseo
will continue to be news of the heart and that's it
seguirá siendo de noticias del corazón y
and if I have to give my opinion about
punto y si tengo que opinar algo de
someone be it a youtuber a journalist or
alguien ya sea youtuber sea periodista o
whatever it is I'm going to continue doing it
sea lo que sea lo voy a seguir haciendo
I don't care about the crying family what do
me da igual los lloros familia que
you think of this disappointment not to
pensáis ustedes de esta decepción no de
fall into insults and
caer en el insulto y en la falta de
disrespect I'll be reading you see you
respeto os estaré leyendo nos vemos
tomorrow
mañana